# Jeremiah E. Lopez

#### Resume

# **Work Experience**

#### Sandwich Maker | Panera Bread

June 2024 - Aug. 2024

- Handle customer orders courteously and accurately, ensuring that all orders are prepared according to customer specifications
- Have the ability to pay attention to detail, and work in a fast-paced environment with organization skills

#### **Delivery Driver | Jimmy Johns**

September 2022 - February 2023 | November 2023 - April 2024

- Responsible for performing all job duties accurately, safely and with honesty and integrity
- Ask for feedback on provided services and resolve clients' complaints
- Be prompt, tactful, calm, courteous, and professional in all interactions

#### Customer Associate | Raising

Canes April 2023 - Nov. 2023

- Responsible for performing all job duties accurately, safely and with honesty and integrity
- Evaluate employee performance to gauge where skills are lacking and provide feedback
- Be prompt, tactful, calm, courteous, and professional in all interactions

# **Education**



### **Glendale Community College - 2 Years**

Class of 2024

4 Semesters consisting average of 4 Classes each. Joined Maricopa Honors Society and Phi Theta Kappa Honors Society. Participated Cinema Society Club as Senator.



**Thunderbird High School** Class of 2022 Relevant Coursework: Honors English, Honors Algebra, Honors Geometry, College Algebra, Honors Integrated Science, Honors Biology, Honors Chemistry.



Pharmacy Technician Program - West-Mec Class of 2022

This one year hands-on course teaches the basics of pharmacy duties while also performing them in a practice lab for 450 hours of classroom and lab instruction.

jeremyllllopez3789@gmail.com 602-469-6844

# **Personal Profile**

A fast-learning individual who is patient and a good problem-solver. Currently enrolled in a Northern Arizona University as a work/study student. Involved in many years of honors programs and participating in extracurricular activities such a film club.

#### **Skills**

- Able to physically operate a computer and efficiently use computer programs and applications.
- Able to focus completely on a speaker, understand their message, comprehend the information and respond thoughtfully.
- Able to determine the source of a problem and find an effective solution.
- Able to learn new techniques and methods quickly and apply them efficiently

# **Certifications | Awards**

AZ State Board License, 2022

President's Honor List -Glendale Community College 2022

Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society - 2023

Food Handler Card, 2023